<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</title>
    <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2003 - 2017, Two&#39;s Company LTD; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2999 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://twoscompany.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paul Henry Show</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2999/04/19/paul-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2999 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2999/04/19/paul-henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sasha Madarasz has been interviewed on the Paul Henry show. Not only are we in the midst of the great Kiwi man drought, there&amp;rsquo;s an education gap to boot between the few available men and their higher-qualified female counterparts looking for love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed-responsive embed-responsive-4by3&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe class=&#34;embed-responsive-item&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-kKSr5v4Q3M&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning Two&#39;s Company</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2998/03/19/good-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2998 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2998/03/19/good-morning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sasha Madarasz has been interviewed on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Good Morning show in 2005, 2007 and 2011. She has appeared on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Breakfast show in 2007 and &lt;sup&gt;20&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;20&lt;/sub&gt; in 2005. Sasha was the Dating expert for Close Up in February 2009 where she successfully blind matched a couple. Sasha Madarasz has been writing dating advice for The Parnell Darling Magazine since 2005, Verge Magazine since 2011 and the 3News Website since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed-responsive embed-responsive-4by3&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe class=&#34;embed-responsive-item&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-AC75mxHQFA&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT WOMEN WANT!</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/10/23/what-women-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/10/23/what-women-want/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For time immemorial men have been asking one question; &lt;strong&gt;one BIG question; &amp;ldquo;What do women want?!!!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; There have been many books and even movies written in an attempt to answer this question. However if you have ever found yourself wondering what women are really looking for, more likely than not all the books written exploring this subject are by American authors for Americans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my 14 years of running &lt;strong&gt;Two&amp;rsquo;s Company&lt;/strong&gt;, an introduction agency for busy Kiwi’s, it has become clear to me that Kiwi women and men are worlds away from their American counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Two&amp;rsquo;s Company I organise 80 to 100 dates every week. I do follow ups after every first date. &lt;strong&gt;I get a lot of feedback!&lt;/strong&gt; When I sign up a new client I ask them,&amp;ldquo;What is it you are looking for? What are you attracted to? &lt;strong&gt;What do you want from a man?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; With all of this information at my fingertips, it has become apparent that there are some common threads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So&amp;hellip;if you really want to know what women are looking for read on!&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;figure class=&#34;responsivemdimage&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://twoscompany.github.io/img/press/www/menu.jpeg&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may come as a surprise to know for instance that the vast majority of women are looking for &lt;strong&gt;a man who has his own life and his own friends!&lt;/strong&gt; Contrary to the popular myth that women want to lock their men away, the truth is women want to know that their men are respected by their friends and peers and that they enjoy their own lives and hobbies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems that a lot of guys out there think women want a man with a BIG FAT wallet, huge arms, great shoulders and a six pack&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;But &lt;strong&gt;NO! NO! NO!&lt;/strong&gt; Overall every woman wants &lt;strong&gt;someone who is happy in their own skin.&lt;/strong&gt; Perfect looks and bodies are more what men are into. &lt;strong&gt;Women fall in love with the whole package; the character, humour, wit, reliability, trustworthiness, intellect and of course the hundreds of little ways he loves her.&lt;/strong&gt; A lightning bolt flashes through our minds as we realise that &amp;ldquo;this man is a &lt;strong&gt;good&lt;/strong&gt; man&amp;rdquo;. From there any man will transform magically in her eyes into the most gorgeous guy ever to walk the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a man doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like George Clooney or have a bank account to match, yet they are happy with what they do have, that makes them very attractive!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a man is &lt;strong&gt;successful and happy in the work he is doing&lt;/strong&gt;, whatever that may be, that is great. If not as long as he is actively making plans or setting goals to achieve success in this area that will satisfy him&amp;hellip;it&amp;rsquo;s all good!!

&lt;figure class=&#34;responsivemdimage&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://twoscompany.github.io/img/press/www/sunset.jpeg&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now a big issue for women is in wanting a man who is &lt;strong&gt;a decision maker with the initiative needed to make plans&lt;/strong&gt;. While women are totally capable of making plans for a weekend away, booking restaurants and organising dinner parties with friends; it &lt;strong&gt;totally rocks their world&lt;/strong&gt; when their men do it. There are hundreds of ways to demonstrate your love for her and her value to you&amp;hellip;plus, it screams &lt;strong&gt;ROMANCE!&lt;/strong&gt; Doing this will never fail to make her desire you in ways that you would never imagine!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yes &lt;strong&gt;Boys, a sense of humour is very high on the list&lt;/strong&gt;. Life does have a way of throwing curve balls at us all, this ability to laugh through the hard times is about as valuable as diamonds. If you can go one step further and &lt;strong&gt;get her to laugh&lt;/strong&gt;, even when she’s a bit cross and doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to &amp;hellip;you become irresistible!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what do women want?&lt;/strong&gt; A wise woman I know once said &amp;ldquo;be you, be free, be it with me&amp;rdquo;. We do not want to change your entire lives and lock you away from the world. &lt;strong&gt;We love your passion for life, your friends, families and hobbies&lt;/strong&gt;. The things that you are interested in make you who you are&amp;hellip;the men that we love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When all is said and done if we as women know with absolute certainty that &lt;strong&gt;our man loves and values us&lt;/strong&gt; then we my friends are &lt;strong&gt;putty in your hands&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class=&#34;responsivemdimage&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://twoscompany.github.io/img/press/www/heart.jpeg&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you’re currently single and looking for someone fabulous, let &lt;strong&gt;Two’s Company&lt;/strong&gt; take the guesswork out of dating by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twoscompany.github.io/contact&#34;&gt;contacting&lt;/a&gt; us now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go On A Date Think Like A Matchmaker</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/02/04/go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/02/04/go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today more than ever it is so easy to meet people from all around the world without leaving your doorstep. When online dating became available there was hope that finding love would be a brief and brisk affair. Unfortunately the opposite occurred. Finding and recognizing true love has turned out to be a much more challenging journey, more than it was in our parents’ generation. The growing number of singles in our modern society proves this sad reality. Becoming aware of this situation, I thought it would be interesting to hear advice from professional matchmakers from different countries who have proven success in their field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://aforlifestyle.blogspot.co.nz/2015/02/go-on-date-think-like-matchmaker_3.html&#34;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiwis dating in the 21st century, no digital boundaries</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/01/13/kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2017/01/13/kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;They want Kiwis&amp;rsquo;
Sasha Madarasz, 42, set up dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company 13 years ago to a booming industry. She said it used to just be the 50+ age bracket who were using her match-making skills but &amp;gt; now she&amp;rsquo;s getting people as young as 23 asking to be set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The age bracket that&amp;rsquo;s booming is the 25 to 45 range. In the past five years, or even three, it&amp;rsquo;s really skyrocketed.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nzh.tw/11757071&#34;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Educational man drought&#39;: Slim pickings in schooled men</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/05/03/educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/05/03/educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland match-making agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company, said many of her clients were professional women seeking compatible men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nzh.tw/11442373&#34;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual man drought foils search for Mr Right</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/05/03/intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right---copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/05/03/intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right---copy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too often, they are narrowing their pool of potential partners by insisting on matching with educational equals, says Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nzh.tw/11442338&#34;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Cinderella to casual sex</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/02/14/from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/press/2015/02/14/from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Owner Sasha Madarasz says at any one time she has around 600 clients looking for love, the majority between the ages 30 and 45. In this age group, there has been a renewed demand for old-fashioned matchmaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.stuff.co.nz/life-style/love-sex/66159885/from-cinderella-to-casual-sex&#34;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;we-are-here-to-help-you&#34;&gt;We are here to help you&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to know more about our service, please send us an enquiry. Your personal information is totally protected, and we will never share any of your details under any circumstance. You can also call us on 0800 021 522 or email Sasha.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t found the answer for your question please feel free to contact us, our customer support will be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/fees/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Stories</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/stories/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;see-what-others-are-saying&#34;&gt;See what others are saying&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellington</title>
      <link>https://twoscompany.github.io/wellington/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twoscompany.github.io/wellington/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;wellington-you-asked-and-now-we-re-here&#34;&gt;Wellington, you asked and now we&amp;rsquo;re here! &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have been helping people meet their ideal match in Auckland since 2003.
Over the years the number of requests we&amp;rsquo;ve had from Wellingtonians has inspired me to bring our unique matchmaking to your beautiful city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twoscompany.github.io/contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; us now to make a time for a no obligation coffee. With me. In Wellington.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re offering a special deal for Wellington clients. Be quick, it&amp;rsquo;s only till Christmas!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>