<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</title>
    <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 13:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://twoscompany.co.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go On A Date Think Like A Matchmaker</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</guid>
      <description>Today more than ever it is so easy to meet people from all around the world without leaving your doorstep. When online dating became available there was hope that finding love would be a brief and brisk affair. Unfortunately the opposite occurred. Finding and recognizing true love has turned out to be a much more challenging journey, more than it was in our parents’ generation. The growing number of singles in our modern society proves this sad reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiwis dating in the 21st century, no digital boundaries</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;They want Kiwis&amp;rsquo; Sasha Madarasz, 42, set up dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company 13 years ago to a booming industry. She said it used to just be the 50+ age bracket who were using her match-making skills but &amp;gt; now she&amp;rsquo;s getting people as young as 23 asking to be set up.
  &amp;ldquo;The age bracket that&amp;rsquo;s booming is the 25 to 45 range. In the past five years, or even three, it&amp;rsquo;s really skyrocketed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Educational man drought&#39;: Slim pickings in schooled men</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</guid>
      <description> Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland match-making agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company, said many of her clients were professional women seeking compatible men.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual man drought foils search for Mr Right</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right-copy/</guid>
      <description> Too often, they are narrowing their pool of potential partners by insisting on matching with educational equals, says Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Cinderella to casual sex</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</guid>
      <description> Owner Sasha Madarasz says at any one time she has around 600 clients looking for love, the majority between the ages 30 and 45. In this age group, there has been a renewed demand for old-fashioned matchmaking.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT WOMEN WANT!</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/what-women-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/what-women-want/</guid>
      <description>For time immemorial men have been asking one question; one BIG question; &amp;ldquo;What do women want?!!!&amp;quot; There have been many books and even movies written in an attempt to answer this question. However if you have ever found yourself wondering what women are really looking for, more likely than not all the books written exploring this subject are by American authors for Americans.
In my 14 years of running Two&amp;rsquo;s Company, an introduction agency for busy Kiwi’s, it has become clear to me that Kiwi women and men are worlds away from their American counterparts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you If you’d like to know more about our service, please send us an enquiry. Your personal information is totally protected, and we will never share any of your details under any circumstance. You can also call us on 0800 021 522 or email Sasha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dating in lock down</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/lockdown/</guid>
      <description>This may seem like a funny time to be meeting new people, however it might just be the perfect time.
Keeping safe doesn’t have to mean being isolated. No, we are not allowed to leave our bubble, but if you are single and wanting to meet someone, it can still happen.
As my clients know, I am big on people not judging someone after one date. We have a two date ‘encouragement’ because this gives you time to get to know someone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/faq/</guid>
      <description>  In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t found the answer for your question please feel free to contact us, our customer support will be happy to help you.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/fees/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Stories</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/stories/</guid>
      <description>See what others are saying </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellington</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/wellington/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/wellington/</guid>
      <description>Wellington, you asked and now we&amp;rsquo;re here!  We have been helping people meet their ideal match in Auckland since 2003. Over the years the number of requests we&amp;rsquo;ve had from Wellingtonians has inspired me to bring our unique matchmaking to your beautiful city.
Contact us now to make a time for a no obligation coffee. With me. In Wellington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>