<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Press on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</title>
    <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/categories/press/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Press on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://twoscompany.co.nz/categories/press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The AM Show - Dating In Lockdown</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/1.-dating-suring-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/1.-dating-suring-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>Are you single and getting a bit lonely? Well what a better time to get to know someone than in lockdown.
Obviously we can&amp;rsquo;t actually meet potential lovers in person just yet but thanks to the internet and video calling apps we&amp;rsquo;re still able to interact with those outside our bubble.
To give us the rules and guidelines on online dating is Two&amp;rsquo;s Company Owner Sasha Madarasz spoke to The AM Show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paul Henry Show</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/2.-paul-henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/2.-paul-henry/</guid>
      <description>Sasha Madarasz has been interviewed on the Paul Henry show. Not only are we in the midst of the great Kiwi man drought, there&amp;rsquo;s an education gap to boot between the few available men and their higher-qualified female counterparts looking for love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio - Dating In Lockdown</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/3.-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/3.-radio/</guid>
      <description>Listen to Sasha on Radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning Two&#39;s Company</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/4.-good-morning-2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/4.-good-morning-2005/</guid>
      <description>Sasha Madarasz has been interviewed on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Good Morning show in 2005, 2007 and 2011. She has appeared on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Breakfast show in 2007 and 20/20 in 2005. Sasha was the Dating expert for Close Up in February 2009 where she successfully blind matched a couple. Sasha Madarasz has been writing dating advice for The Parnell Darling Magazine since 2005, Verge Magazine since 2011 and the 3News Website since 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning Two&#39;s Company</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/5.-good-morning-2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/5.-good-morning-2007/</guid>
      <description>Sasha Madarasz has been interviewed on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Good Morning show in 2005, 2007 and 2011. She has appeared on TV One&amp;rsquo;s Breakfast show in 2007 and 20/20 in 2005. Sasha was the Dating expert for Close Up in February 2009 where she successfully blind matched a couple. Sasha Madarasz has been writing dating advice for The Parnell Darling Magazine since 2005, Verge Magazine since 2011 and the 3News Website since 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do if you forgot about Valentine&#39;s Day?</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/6.-newstalkzb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/6.-newstalkzb/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, which means roses, chocolates and romantic dinners are all in store for many of you today.
But for those of you out there who have completely forgotten - don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help.
Founder of dating website Two&amp;rsquo;s Company Sasha Madarasz told Mike Hosking there are a few things you can do last minute to make up for it.
From fish and chips picnic at home to rekindling your youth with fun activities like roller skating, there are several ways you can turn forgetfulness on its head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Younger people more attracted to dating agencies</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/7.-nzheraldvalentines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/7.-nzheraldvalentines/</guid>
      <description>Tinder has become a slippery slope into dating agencies for the younger crowd.
Five years ago around 20 people under 30 were looking for love through dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company. Now that number hovers around 80.
Agency director Sasha Madarasz spoke to the Herald ahead of Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day this Wednesday.
In the last five years, Madarasz had seen a huge shift in younger people using dating agencies. Most of her clients used to be in the 37 to 55 age range, now they&amp;rsquo;re in the 25 to 40 age range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand’s Most Selective Dating Agency Connects Singles Throughout New Zealand</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/8.-dating-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/8.-dating-advice/</guid>
      <description> After years of running a talent agency, Sasha Madarasz felt ready to get out of the fast-paced film industry and make more of a difference in the world. She just didn’t know how she would do that. The answer came from her boyfriend at the time, who suggested she start a dating agency.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go On A Date Think Like A Matchmaker</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/9.-go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/9.-go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</guid>
      <description>Today more than ever it is so easy to meet people from all around the world without leaving your doorstep. When online dating became available there was hope that finding love would be a brief and brisk affair. Unfortunately the opposite occurred. Finding and recognizing true love has turned out to be a much more challenging journey, more than it was in our parents’ generation. The growing number of singles in our modern society proves this sad reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiwis dating in the 21st century, no digital boundaries</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/10.-kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/10.-kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;They want Kiwis&amp;rsquo; Sasha Madarasz, 42, set up dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company 13 years ago to a booming industry. She said it used to just be the 50+ age bracket who were using her match-making skills but &amp;gt; now she&amp;rsquo;s getting people as young as 23 asking to be set up.
  &amp;ldquo;The age bracket that&amp;rsquo;s booming is the 25 to 45 range. In the past five years, or even three, it&amp;rsquo;s really skyrocketed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Educational man drought&#39;: Slim pickings in schooled men</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/11.-educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/11.-educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</guid>
      <description> Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland match-making agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company, said many of her clients were professional women seeking compatible men.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual man drought foils search for Mr Right</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/12.-intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/12.-intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right/</guid>
      <description> Too often, they are narrowing their pool of potential partners by insisting on matching with educational equals, says Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Cinderella to casual sex</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/13.-from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/13.-from-cinderella-to-casual-sex/</guid>
      <description> Owner Sasha Madarasz says at any one time she has around 600 clients looking for love, the majority between the ages 30 and 45. In this age group, there has been a renewed demand for old-fashioned matchmaking.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>