<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NZHerald on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</title>
    <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/tags/nzherald/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NZHerald on Dating Service Auckland and Wellington | Dating Agency | Introduction Agency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://twoscompany.co.nz/tags/nzherald/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Younger people more attracted to dating agencies</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/7.-nzheraldvalentines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/7.-nzheraldvalentines/</guid>
      <description>Tinder has become a slippery slope into dating agencies for the younger crowd.
Five years ago around 20 people under 30 were looking for love through dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company. Now that number hovers around 80.
Agency director Sasha Madarasz spoke to the Herald ahead of Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day this Wednesday.
In the last five years, Madarasz had seen a huge shift in younger people using dating agencies. Most of her clients used to be in the 37 to 55 age range, now they&amp;rsquo;re in the 25 to 40 age range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go On A Date Think Like A Matchmaker</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/9.-go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/9.-go-on-a-date-think-like-a-matchmaker/</guid>
      <description>Today more than ever it is so easy to meet people from all around the world without leaving your doorstep. When online dating became available there was hope that finding love would be a brief and brisk affair. Unfortunately the opposite occurred. Finding and recognizing true love has turned out to be a much more challenging journey, more than it was in our parents’ generation. The growing number of singles in our modern society proves this sad reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiwis dating in the 21st century, no digital boundaries</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/10.-kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/10.-kiwis-dating-in-the-21st-century-no-digital-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;They want Kiwis&amp;rsquo; Sasha Madarasz, 42, set up dating agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company 13 years ago to a booming industry. She said it used to just be the 50+ age bracket who were using her match-making skills but &amp;gt; now she&amp;rsquo;s getting people as young as 23 asking to be set up.
  &amp;ldquo;The age bracket that&amp;rsquo;s booming is the 25 to 45 range. In the past five years, or even three, it&amp;rsquo;s really skyrocketed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Educational man drought&#39;: Slim pickings in schooled men</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/11.-educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/11.-educational-man-drought-slim-pickings-in-schooled-men/</guid>
      <description> Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland match-making agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company, said many of her clients were professional women seeking compatible men.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual man drought foils search for Mr Right</title>
      <link>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/12.-intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twoscompany.co.nz/press/12.-intellectual-man-drought-foils-search-for-mr-right/</guid>
      <description> Too often, they are narrowing their pool of potential partners by insisting on matching with educational equals, says Sasha Madarasz, owner of Auckland agency Two&amp;rsquo;s Company.
 See more</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>